<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  Central page content.

  Edit THIS single file to customize any page's content without touching the
  individual page files (*.aspx / *.aspx.cs).

  How it works
  ============
  Each page's LoadPageContent() sets the built-in default content. Anything you
  define here takes priority over that default AND over Web.config "Page.*"
  appSettings. So the precedence is:

      this file (PageContent.xml)  >  Web.config "Page.*"  >  LoadPageContent() defaults

  Changes here take effect immediately (the file is watched); no rebuild needed.

  Structure
  =========
    <page key="Default" title="Optional browser title">
        <box id="cbWelcome" header="Optional header text"><![CDATA[
            Any HTML for this ContentBox goes here.
        ]]></box>
        <literal id="litSomething"><![CDATA[ text for a Literal control ]]></literal>
    </page>

    - key    = page class name (e.g. Default, About, FAQ, Donations, Privacy,
               Legal, ReadThisFirst).
    - box id / literal id = the control's ID as it appears in the .aspx markup.
    - Put HTML inside <![CDATA[ ... ]]> so you don't have to escape < > & or quotes.
    - "header" attribute is optional; omit it to keep the header from the markup.

  Available control IDs per page
  ==============================
    Default        : cbWelcome, cbAbout, cbFeatures, cbGetStarted
    About          : cbAbout, cbHowItWorks, cbHistory, cbContact, cbLegal
    FAQ            : cbGeneral, cbCompatibility, cbUpdates
    Donations      : cbSupport, cbHowToHelp
    Privacy        : cbInfoCollect, cbInfoUse, cbDataSecurity, cbContact
    Legal          : cbDisclaimer, cbLicense, cbTrademarks, cbLiability
    ReadThisFirst  : cbTOC, cbDisclaimer, cbWelcome, cbFeatures, cbStarted

  Example (remove the surrounding comment to activate):

    <page key="Default">
        <box id="cbWelcome" header="Welcome!"><![CDATA[
            <p>Your custom welcome text here.</p>
        ]]></box>
    </page>
-->
<content>

  <page key="Default">
    <box id="cbWelcome" header="Welcome!"><![CDATA[
Welcome to this Windows XP styled website template! 
                This template provides a nostalgic look reminiscent of classic Windows XP/2000 era websites. 
                The layout uses a frame-based design with a top toolbar, navigation sidebar, and main content area.
                <br /><br />
                Feel free to customize the navigation, content, and styling to match your needs.
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbAbout" header="About This Site"><![CDATA[
This template is designed to provide an authentic retro computing aesthetic. 
                Key features include:
                <ul>
                    <li>Windows XP/2000 era styling and colors</li>
                    <li>Frame-based layout with toolbar and sidebar navigation</li>
                    <li>Reusable content box controls and layout</li>
                    <li>Generic and customizable structure</li>
                    <li>ASP.NET Web Forms architecture</li>
                </ul>
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbFeatures" header="Key Features"><![CDATA[
<b>Template Features:</b>
                <ul class='feature-list'>
                    <li><b>Master Page Layout</b> - Consistent frame-based structure across all pages</li>
                    <li><b>Navigation Control</b> - Configurable sidebar navigation with sections</li>
                    <li><b>Toolbar Control</b> - Logo and branding via Web.config</li>
                    <li><b>Content Box Control</b> - Reusable styled content containers</li>
                    <li><b>Footer Control</b> - Copyright text via Web.config</li>
                    <li><b>Responsive Design</b> - Works on various screen sizes</li>
                </ul>
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbGetStarted" header="Getting Started"><![CDATA[
<b>To customize this template:</b>
                <ul>
                    <li>Edit <code>Web.config</code> appSettings for logo, site name, footer, and page content</li>
                    <li>Set <code>ContentHtml</code> directly on ContentBox controls in .aspx markup</li>
                    <li>Override any page box via <code>Page.{PageKey}.{ControlId}.ContentHtml</code> in Web.config</li>
                    <li>Modify <code>Navigationbar.ascx.cs</code> to customize navigation items</li>
                    <li>Add new content pages inheriting from <code>BasePage</code></li>
                </ul>
                <br />
                <i>This template is ready for use as a starting point for Windows XP styled websites!</i>
    ]]></box>
  </page>

  <page key="About">
    <box id="cbAbout" header="What is this project about?"><![CDATA[
This project demonstrates how to create a Windows XP styled website using ASP.NET Web Forms. 
                The template provides a nostalgic look reminiscent of classic Windows XP/2000 era websites, bringing back the 
                authentic feel of early 2000s web design.
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbHowItWorks" header="How does it work?"><![CDATA[
The template uses a master page with frame-based layout simulation using CSS flexbox. 
                The navigation is handled through a configurable user control that allows easy customization of menu items.
                Content is displayed through reusable content box controls that maintain consistent styling.
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbHistory" header="The history of the project"><![CDATA[
This template was created to help developers build retro-styled websites that capture 
                the essence of the Windows XP/2000 era. It's perfect for nostalgia projects, retro computing enthusiasts, 
                or anyone looking to create an authentic early 2000s web experience.
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbContact" header="Get in touch with us!"><![CDATA[
If you would like to contact us for any reason, you can do so through the following channels:
                <br /><br />
                <b>Email:</b> <a href='mailto:contact@example.com'>contact@example.com</a>
                <br />
                <b>Website:</b> <a href='../Default.aspx'>Home Page</a>
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbLegal" header="Privacy Policy and Legal Information"><![CDATA[
Learn more about how your data is used and the legal side of this website by visiting the 
                <a href='Privacy.aspx'>Privacy Policy</a> and <a href='Legal.aspx'>Legal Information</a> pages.
    ]]></box>
  </page>

  <page key="FAQ">
    <box id="cbGeneral" header="General Project Questions"><![CDATA[
                <div class='faq-question'>What is this template for?</div>
                <div class='faq-answer'>This template is designed for creating Windows XP/2000 styled websites using ASP.NET Web Forms. It provides an authentic retro computing aesthetic.</div>
                
                <div class='faq-question'>Is this template free to use?</div>
                <div class='faq-answer'>Yes, this template is provided as a starting point for your own projects. Feel free to customize it to your needs.</div>
                
                <div class='faq-question'>What technologies does this template use?</div>
                <div class='faq-answer'>This template uses ASP.NET Web Forms with C# code-behind, master pages, user controls, and CSS for styling.</div>
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbCompatibility" header="Compatibility &amp; Operating Systems"><![CDATA[
                <div class='faq-question'>What browsers are supported?</div>
                <div class='faq-answer'>The template is designed to work with modern browsers while maintaining the classic Windows XP aesthetic. It uses standard HTML and CSS.</div>
                
                <div class='faq-question'>Does this work on mobile devices?</div>
                <div class='faq-answer'>Yes, the template includes responsive CSS that adapts to smaller screens while maintaining the retro look on desktop.</div>
                
                <div class='faq-question'>Can I customize the colors?</div>
                <div class='faq-answer'>Absolutely! All colors are defined in CSS and can be easily modified to match your preferred color scheme.</div>
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbUpdates" header="Updates &amp; Contributing"><![CDATA[
                <div class='faq-question'>How do I add new pages?</div>
                <div class='faq-answer'>Create a new Web Form that uses the Site.Master master page and inherits from BasePage. Add your content to the MainContent placeholder.</div>
                
                <div class='faq-question'>How do I change the logo?</div>
                <div class='faq-answer'>Edit SiteLogoUrl, SiteLogoWidth, SiteLogoHeight, and SiteLogoAlt in Web.config appSettings. No code changes required.</div>
                
                <div class='faq-question'>How do I override page content?</div>
                <div class='faq-answer'>Set ContentHtml on ContentBox controls in .aspx markup, or add Page.{PageKey}.{ControlId}.ContentHtml keys in Web.config.</div>
    ]]></box>
  </page>

  <page key="Donations">
    <box id="cbSupport" header="Support This Project"><![CDATA[
This template is provided free of charge. If you find it useful for your projects, 
                consider making a donation to support continued development and maintenance.
                <br /><br />
                Your support helps cover hosting costs and allows us to dedicate more time to improving the template.
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbHowToHelp" header="Other Ways to Help"><![CDATA[
Not able to donate? There are other ways you can help:
                <ul>
                    <li><b>Spread the word</b> - Share this template with others who might find it useful</li>
                    <li><b>Report bugs</b> - Help us improve by reporting any issues you encounter</li>
                    <li><b>Contribute code</b> - Submit improvements and new features</li>
                    <li><b>Provide feedback</b> - Let us know how we can make this template better</li>
                </ul>
    ]]></box>
  </page>

  <page key="Legal">
    <box id="cbDisclaimer" header="Disclaimer"><![CDATA[
<font color='#660000'>
                <b>THIS SOFTWARE IS PROVIDED "AS IS", WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY KIND, EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, 
                INCLUDING BUT NOT LIMITED TO THE WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR 
                PURPOSE AND NONINFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL THE AUTHORS OR COPYRIGHT HOLDERS BE LIABLE 
                FOR ANY CLAIM, DAMAGES OR OTHER LIABILITY, WHETHER IN AN ACTION OF CONTRACT, TORT OR 
                OTHERWISE, ARISING FROM, OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE SOFTWARE OR THE USE OR OTHER 
                DEALINGS IN THE SOFTWARE.</b>
                </font>
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbLicense" header="License"><![CDATA[
This template is provided for educational and personal use. 
                You are free to:
                <ul>
                    <li>Use this template for your own projects</li>
                    <li>Modify and customize the code to suit your needs</li>
                    <li>Distribute copies to others</li>
                </ul>
                <br />
                Please retain any copyright notices and attributions when using this template.
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbTrademarks" header="Trademarks"><![CDATA[
Windows, Windows XP, and other Microsoft product names are trademarks or 
                registered trademarks of Microsoft Corporation in the United States and/or other countries.
                <br /><br />
                This template is not affiliated with, endorsed, sponsored, or specifically approved by Microsoft Corporation.
                <br /><br />
                All other trademarks mentioned are the property of their respective owners.
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbLiability" header="Limitation of Liability"><![CDATA[
The developers of this template shall not be held liable for any direct, 
                indirect, incidental, special, exemplary, or consequential damages arising from the use of this template.
                <br /><br />
                Users are responsible for ensuring their use of this template complies with applicable laws and regulations.
                <br /><br />
                <i>This template is provided for convenience and educational purposes. Use at your own risk.</i>
    ]]></box>
  </page>

  <page key="Privacy">
    <box id="cbInfoCollect" header="Information We Collect"><![CDATA[
We collect minimal information necessary to provide our services:
                <ul>
                    <li><b>Usage Data:</b> Anonymous usage statistics to improve our services</li>
                    <li><b>Contact Information:</b> If you contact us, we may store your email for correspondence</li>
                    <li><b>Cookies:</b> Essential cookies for site functionality</li>
                </ul>
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbInfoUse" header="How We Use Your Information"><![CDATA[
The information we collect is used to:
                <ul>
                    <li>Provide and maintain our services</li>
                    <li>Improve user experience</li>
                    <li>Respond to inquiries and support requests</li>
                    <li>Send important notifications about our services</li>
                </ul>
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbDataSecurity" header="Data Security"><![CDATA[
We implement appropriate security measures to protect your information:
                <ul>
                    <li>SSL/TLS encryption for data transmission</li>
                    <li>Regular security assessments</li>
                    <li>Limited access to personal data</li>
                </ul>
                <br />
                <i>Note: No method of transmission over the Internet is 100% secure. We strive to protect your data but cannot guarantee absolute security.</i>
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbContact" header="Contact Us"><![CDATA[
If you have questions about this privacy policy, please contact us:
                <br /><br />
                <b>Email:</b> <a href='mailto:privacy@example.com'>privacy@example.com</a>
    ]]></box>
  </page>

  <page key="ReadThisFirst">
    <box id="cbTOC" header="Table of Contents"><![CDATA[
                <ul class='toc-list'>
                    <li><b><a href='#disclaimer'>Disclaimer and Important Notices</a></b></li>
                    <li><b><a href='#welcome'>Welcome!</a></b></li>
                    <li><b><a href='#features'>Key Features</a></b></li>
                    <li><b><a href='#started'>Getting Started</a></b></li>
                </ul>
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbDisclaimer" header="Disclaimer and Important Notices"><![CDATA[
                <font color='#660000'>
                    <b>This template is provided "as is", without warranty of any kind. 
                    While we've tested it thoroughly, please ensure you have backups of any important data. 
                    This template is for educational and personal use.</b>
                </font>
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbWelcome" header="Welcome!"><![CDATA[
                Thank you for using this Windows XP styled website template! 
                This template is designed to help developers create retro-styled websites with an authentic 
                Windows XP/2000 era look and feel.
                <br /><br />
                The template uses ASP.NET Web Forms with master pages, user controls, and CSS to recreate 
                the classic frame-based layout that was common in early 2000s websites.
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbFeatures" header="Key Features"><![CDATA[
                <b>Template Features:</b>
                <ul>
                    <li><b>Master Page Layout</b> - Consistent frame-based structure</li>
                    <li><b>Navigation Control</b> - Configurable sidebar navigation</li>
                    <li><b>Content Boxes</b> - Reusable styled content containers</li>
                    <li><b>Retro Styling</b> - Authentic Windows XP aesthetic</li>
                    <li><b>Responsive Design</b> - Works on modern devices</li>
                    <li><b>Easy Customization</b> - Web.config and markup overrides</li>
                </ul>
    ]]></box>
    <box id="cbStarted" header="Getting Started"><![CDATA[
                To get started with this template:
                <br /><br />
                <b>1.</b> Open the project in Visual Studio
                <br />
                <b>2.</b> Build and run the project
                <br />
                <b>3.</b> Customize logo and site name in <code>Web.config</code>
                <br />
                <b>4.</b> Add your content pages using the master page and <code>BasePage</code>
                <br />
                <b>5.</b> Modify the CSS to match your branding
                <br /><br />
                <i>Refer to the FAQ page for more detailed instructions!</i>
    ]]></box>
  </page>

</content>
